<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>theATL.social</title>
    <link>https://about.theatl.social/</link>
    <description>Recent content on theATL.social</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://about.theatl.social/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://about.theatl.social/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://about.theatl.social/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to theATL.social Contribute to theATL.social&amp;rsquo;s operations via Patreon ❤️
About theATL.social is a growing Mastodon server focused on the Atlanta, GA region.
Questions about Mastodon, the Fediverse, ActivityPub, and all the other tech word things? Check out fedi.tips.
Primary Admin Contact Email: michael@theatl.social Mastodon Username: @michael@theatl.social Secondary Admin Contact Email: theatl_admin@sigler.io Mastodon Username: @r@theatl.social Why have an Atlanta-focused server for Mastodon? People typically join small- to medium-sized servers based on some aspect of a server that personally appeals to them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://about.theatl.social/bots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://about.theatl.social/bots/</guid>
      <description>News and RSS Bots Contribute to theATL.social&amp;rsquo;s operations via Patreon ❤️
About test123
&amp;ldquo;Bots&amp;rdquo; are accounts on theATL.social that automatically post news stories or timely information, based on updates to web pages or RSS feeds.
Suggestions and feedback? Send a DM or mention @michael@theatl.social
Update Frequency Bots are typically update every 30 minutes to 1 hour, daily.
How to Follow a Bot Account Search for the account on theATL.social and follow the account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://about.theatl.social/faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://about.theatl.social/faqs/</guid>
      <description>FAQ: Frequently Asked Questions Contribute to theATL.social&amp;rsquo;s operations via Patreon ❤️
Where are your servers located? Are they in Atlanta?
theATL.social operates on the DigitalOcean &amp;ldquo;cloud&amp;rdquo; computing provider, running in a data center in New York City (technically New Jersey).
The choice of provider and data center is due to cost and availability of services. With additional funding, closer data centers to Atlanta may be utilized (for example, the AWS Atlanta local zone).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://about.theatl.social/funding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://about.theatl.social/funding/</guid>
      <description>Funding Contribute to theATL.social&amp;rsquo;s operations via Patreon ❤️
Background Mastodon server costs comprise payment for cloud-based servers, object storage, bandwidth, logging/monitoring, and other auxillary costs. As the number of users on a server increase, the cost per user decreases - an economy of scale.
Current Costs Cost and revenue transparency is provided via a frequently updated Google Sheet.
For information security purposes, some details in the cost spreadsheet are redacted. Full-Text Search (Elastic Search) The server does not currently implement full-text search of posts, due to cost.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
